erin mcbride



web developer & designer

ABOUT

Hardworking web developer/designer with experience creating front-end projects such as a responsive portfolio, online registration form, and an interactive photo gallery. Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. My main goals are furthering my career and doing what's best for my family. Excited to see what's in store for me in the future.

EDUCATION

Radford University

Bachelors of Science in Criminal Justice, 2015

EXPERIENCE

Dell Seton Medical Center at The University of Texas - Temporary Web Publisher *April 2018 - May 2018*

- Populate school's website with information and images using a web CMS.
- Audit digital properties for redundant, erroneous, as well as display issues.
- Web content maintenance and optimization,
- Diagnose and troubleshoot problems, resolving technical challenges in displaying content.

Farm Credit Bank of Texas - IT Data Analyst - Austin, TX

January 2018 - April 2018

- Using statistical methods to analyze data and generate useful business reports
- Use data to create reports that track user access to multiple applications

Strayer University - Registrar Service Specialist - Herndon, VA

July 2016 - December 2017

- Evaluated student's transcripts for basis approval
- Managed the main Registrar email account
- Data entry